You use this X right here to get the, uh oh,
oh my gosh, I just knew about that, hold on.
You know what, I'm gonna search for a solution.
Let's see, video. Maybe this guy can help me.
There we go, hey, hey you, hey, hey. Hey, do
you think you could help me? I accidentally
drew on the screen right here. I don't know
what to do. No, a little bit farther down,
farther down, right there. Yeah, there you go.
Oh, that's not working.
That's making it worse. I'm not sure what to
do here. What's that? Oh. I'm sorry.
That's just getting the cat dirty. That's not
working.
All right, let's, oh, okay, yeah, let's try
that, try that.
Oh. It's OK. Don't worry about it. I don't know
what to do. Oh, you have an idea? Oh, OK. Yeah,
all right. OK, let me try that. Okay, go grab
that for me.
out of the way. Let's see if I can do this.
There we go. OK, after we move this.
There we go, I think that worked. Alright, thanks
for helping me. Oh, oh, yeah, okay. Oh, oh,
sorry. Okay. Oh wait a second. I think the lightsaber
was too hot. Uh oh.
Ah, it's catching on fire.
There we go, finally got rid of it. Alright.